number 26 is I will offer my day-to-day
honesty and integrity to the Buddha this
is one of the refuge valves and I can't
remember which one is that am i a bad
person I'll have to go look it up it
because I think it might be let's see
yeah it is yeah so this refuge valve
which is to put all your hopes in the
objects of Refuge every time you do
something yeah the BAL Caribe jay says
it involves offering your day-to-day
honesty and integrity to the buddhist
okay now that's not what you would
expect so I made it a meditation okay it
it doesn't seem to equal putting all
your trust in the three jewels but
somehow it is and maybe you can meditate
on it and figure it out and tell me when
you get out okay so during this
meditation number 26 think of all the
times you've been honest think of all
the times you've been an honest person
in the last few days few weeks and offer
it to the Buddhist and you are you are
taking refuge you are fulfilling your
refuge vows okay so that's a pleasant
meditation you know all the times I was
honest in the last few weeks a lot of
these are not like
confession where you have to think of
what a bad person you are of course you
are on during these meditations you're
supposed to be thinking all the good
things you're doing okay
it's like complementation